<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tipatch</string>
    <string name="contact">Contact</string>
    <string name="exit">Close App</string>
    <string name="patch_btn">Patch</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="report">Send Report</string>
    
    <string name="part_not_found">Tipatch was unable to find your device\'s recovery partition. Select an image file and flash it instead.</string>
    <string name="part_opt_report">\n\nIf you want your device to be supported in the future, send a device report with the button below. No personal information is contained.</string>

    <string name="contact_mail">kdrag0n@pm.me</string>

    <string name="full_info"><![CDATA[
<h4>What is Tipatch?</h4>
<p><b>Tipatch</b> patches <a href=\"https://twrp.me/\">TWRP</a> recovery to back up your internal storage (emulated SD card), meaning your photos, music, game data, downloads, and more will be <i>saved</i> in backups.</p>

<h4>How do I use Tipatch?</h4>
<p>If your device is <b>rooted</b>, you can patch your currently-installed recovery (both slots if your device is A/B) in-place, without having to download or flash any images.</p>

<p>If you\'re <b>not rooted</b>, don\'t worry! You can still use Tipatch. Simply download your device\'s recovery image, open it in Tipatch, and save the resulting patched image. Then, flash or boot this final image like any other one.</p>

<h4>Effects</h4>
To confirm whether it worked, boot into TWRP. Signs of success are:<br/>

&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• "Data (excl. storage)" becoming "Data (incl. storage)"<br/>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• "Backups of Data do not include…" when backing up becoming "Backups of Data include…"<br/>
&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;• Bigger calculated size of Data in Backup screen, because more is included<br/>

<h4>Problems?</h4>

<p>If Tipatch does not work properly on your device (any of the above signs aren\'t present, or it doesn\'t actually back up the data), please let me know! You can find a Contact button in the menu.</p>

<p><b>Enjoy!</b></p>]]>
    </string>
</resources>
